<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Mark Cheret - Exponential Coach</title><link>https://cheret.de/</link><description>Exponential Coach | Cyber Security Consultant | Maker. Artist. Sculptor.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 12:43:48 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>powerful language</title><link>https://cheret.de/2021/05/powerful-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 12:43:48 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2021/05/powerful-language/</guid><description>To understand the concept of powerful language, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at what powerful language and behaviour is and what it isn&amp;rsquo;t. This way we can gain insight into the difference between the powerful and the unconscious.
What are the powerful and the mighty doing? proclaim postulate prescribe enact command What are the unconscious doing? complain demonstrate protest obey / comply propose / apply Unconscious language: What powerful language isn&amp;rsquo;t Our way of expressing opinions and thoughts has been watered down over the centuries.</description></item><item><title>Productivity Hacks and Team Performance Boosts</title><link>https://cheret.de/2021/05/productivity-hacks-and-team-performance-boosts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 21:58:42 +0200</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2021/05/productivity-hacks-and-team-performance-boosts/</guid><description>&lt;p>How can you apply agile practices that you might know from SCRUM to your daily routine? Can you boost your output while staying motivated, energised, and faithful to your core?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How can you take your team to the next level in a remote working environment? Let me take you on a journey to healthy and sustainable productivity with abundant space for fun, relaxation, and above all - yourself.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>pain and pleasure</title><link>https://cheret.de/2020/08/pain-and-pleasure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 19:51:23 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2020/08/pain-and-pleasure/</guid><description>Achieving deeper levels of fulfilment by choice When looking at punishment and reward in terms of educational methodologies, it’s psychologically proven that rewards are more effective than punishment.1
So far so unsurprising as pleasure promotes a higher state of being than punishment. If everything I believe in turns out to be a shared objective factual experience, that means that there is a natural drive towards a higher state of being, otherwise referred to as the good in every human being, against all odds.</description></item><item><title>the act of creation</title><link>https://cheret.de/2020/07/the-act-of-creation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2020/07/the-act-of-creation/</guid><description>&lt;p>The act of creation is the manifestation of invisible potential into actual tangible reality.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>fear of judgement in expressing emotions</title><link>https://cheret.de/2020/07/fear-of-judgement-in-expressing-emotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:56:28 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2020/07/fear-of-judgement-in-expressing-emotions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fear of judgement in expressing emotions is a very common stance which holds us back from having an honest conversation with others and sometimes even ourselves.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Inspirations 2017</title><link>https://cheret.de/2017/12/inspirations-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2017/12/inspirations-2017/</guid><description>I'm continuing my tradition of reflecting who inspired me in the past year and why.</description></item><item><title>Shape your elevator pitch (Networking Series Part 5)</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/10/shape-your-elevator-pitch-networking-series-part-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 22:24:02 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/10/shape-your-elevator-pitch-networking-series-part-5/</guid><description>Your elevator pitch, that is the way you&amp;rsquo;re introducing yourself, should be something you&amp;rsquo;re working on constantly.
Elevator pitch One of the most important ways to brand yourself and let people know what you do is your elevator pitch. So how do you make sure you can get your message across the right way? How can you start raking in those requests to be hired by the right people you can help best?</description></item><item><title>Branding through events (Networking Series Part 4)</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/10/branding-through-events-networking-series-part-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/10/branding-through-events-networking-series-part-4/</guid><description>The types of events you attend shape your personal branding.
Events overload I know you’re part of at least one group that has something to do with networking. And you also get asked a lot to attend major or minor events. It sometimes feels overwhelming and you can’t decide which events to attend. I’ll give you this tool to make a quick yet informed decision of which of all the events will really be the productive one for you.</description></item><item><title>Bring value first (Networking Series Part 3)</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/10/bring-value-first-networking-series-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 06:00:21 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/10/bring-value-first-networking-series-part-3/</guid><description>Bring value to your network first the rest will come later. Have you built your valuable and strong network already? If so, you know that seeking to bring value to your network first will make the key difference. People experienced in networking will mostly concur. I’ll list different ways of contributing value to your network in just a second.
Contribute according to your abilities People generally want to improve upon their current status.</description></item><item><title>Say goodbye to everyone (Networking Part 2)</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/10/say-goodbye-to-everyone-networking-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/10/say-goodbye-to-everyone-networking-part-2/</guid><description>Now here’s one networking advice I can give you. I’ve had countless opportunities through this seemingly small but impactful gesture. On the surface it’s quite simple: Always say goodbye to everyone when you’re leaving an event! And I know that it’s more complicated than that. Give me a moment to explain, though. It will become essential in your networking toolkit.
Everyone&amp;rsquo;s so busy So you’ve been at this busy event and you only knew half of the people there.</description></item></channel></rss>