<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Blog - Tag - Mark Cheret</title><link>https://cheret.de/tags/blog/</link><description>Blog - Tag - Mark Cheret</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 21:51:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cheret.de/tags/blog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inspirations 2016</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/10/inspirations-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 21:51:13 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/10/inspirations-2016/</guid><description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m convinced that we all have our inspirations. We&rsquo;re inspired by actions, ways of thinking and creations of other people. At least that&rsquo;s what I&rsquo;m experiencing. We socialize all the time and gravitate towards like minded people. The internet has brought us closer together. Everyone can express themselves freely and without any gatekeeper these days. Of course this makes for a lot of content in varying degrees of quality which permanently tries to gain our attention.]]></description></item><item><title>My take on the Brexit</title><link>https://cheret.de/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 21:04:11 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2016/06/my-take-on-the-brexit/</guid><description><![CDATA[In the wake of the recent referendum of the United Kingdom&rsquo;s membership of the European Union which in short was just called &ldquo;Brexit&rdquo; for those in favour of leaving the EU, there has been a lot of buzz online and elsewhere. This of course was to be expected of a vote with the potential of having wide ranging consequences. I&rsquo;d like to call a lot of what&rsquo;s been going on merely &ldquo;noise&rdquo; while trying to distill the essence of it which I&rsquo;d like to call &ldquo;signal&rdquo;.]]></description></item><item><title>I have my domain back!</title><link>https://cheret.de/2014/06/i-have-my-domain-back/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 19:00:17 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2014/06/i-have-my-domain-back/</guid><description><![CDATA[You may or may not know nominet. The .uk domain name registry in the United Kingdom, which was founded by Dr. Willie Black and five others on 14th May 1996 when its predecessor, the &ldquo;Naming Committee&rdquo; was unable to deal with the volume of registrations then being sought under the .uk domain. You may as well know that nominet changed their &ldquo;data quality&rdquo; standards for registrant contacts effective on 7th May 2014.]]></description></item><item><title>my take on "Caprica"</title><link>https://cheret.de/2014/02/my-take-on-caprica/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://cheret.de/2014/02/my-take-on-caprica/</guid><description><![CDATA[After having recently finished the &ldquo;Reimagined Battlestar Galactica&rdquo; Series (=BSG), it&rsquo;s only logical to carry on watching one of the two prequels that were produced after BSG has aired. These are &ldquo;Battlestar Galactica: Blood &amp; Chrome&rdquo; and &ldquo;Caprica&rdquo;. I decided to watch Caprica first and Blood and Chrome straight after that. As I recently finished watching &ldquo;Caprica&rdquo;, here&rsquo;s my write-up of thoughts on that particular show.
Background information The pilot episode of Caprica is set 58 years before the story of BSG and was released direct to DVD on 21st April 2009.]]></description></item></channel></rss>