<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Mark Cheret</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Mark Cheret</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under the MIT License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 15:36:53 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://new.cheret.de/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fear of judgement in expressing emotions</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2020/07/fear-of-judgement-in-expressing-emotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 11:56:28 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2020/07/fear-of-judgement-in-expressing-emotions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fear of judgement in expressing emotions is a very common stance which holds us back from having an honest conversation with others and sometimes even ourselves.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the all hyped up .uk top level domain</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2014/06/the-all-hyped-up-.uk-top-level-domain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 20:37:08 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2014/06/the-all-hyped-up-.uk-top-level-domain/</guid><description>.uk is the Internet country code top-level domain (ccTLD) for the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland. As of March 2012, it is the fourth most popular top-level domain worldwide (after .com, .de and .net), with over 10 million registrations. Starting 10th June 2014 it is now possible to register domains ending with a plain .uk. People may have wondered for ages as to why there were only .</description></item><item><title>my take on "The Reimagined Battlestar Galactica"</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2014/01/my-take-on-the-reimagined-battlestar-galactica/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 19:26:49 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2014/01/my-take-on-the-reimagined-battlestar-galactica/</guid><description>Coming from a perspective of being one of many serious Star Trek fans who have watched absolutely every episode and movie there is out there, presently I can't tell which of these I like better.</description></item><item><title>My first post with a new CMS</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 15:36:53 +0100</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2021/03/my-first-post-with-a-new-cms/</guid><description><![CDATA[after more than a decade Just so you know, I&rsquo;ve been a WordPress user, admin, and plugin author for more than a decade now. I could&rsquo;ve set this up as yet another one of those ubiquitous WordPress pages. This time, however, I&rsquo;m taking a different approach. HUGO is my tool of choice as I&rsquo;m a DevSecOps Advisor, leaning into Infrastructure as Code (IaC) and of course the automation behind this declarative setup.]]></description></item><item><title>The act of creation</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2020/07/the-act-of-creation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2020/07/the-act-of-creation/</guid><description>&lt;p>The act of creation is the manifestation of invisible potential into actual tangible reality.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Inspirations 2017</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2017/12/inspirations-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 15:50:44 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2017/12/inspirations-2017/</guid><description>I'm continuing my tradition of reflecting who inspired me in the past year and why.</description></item><item><title>Shape your elevator pitch (Networking Series Part 5)</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/shape-your-elevator-pitch-networking-series-part-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 22:24:02 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/shape-your-elevator-pitch-networking-series-part-5/</guid><description>Your elevator pitch, that is the way you&amp;rsquo;re introducing yourself, should be something you&amp;rsquo;re working on constantly.
Elevator pitch One of the most important ways to brand yourself and let people know what you do is your elevator pitch. So how do you make sure you can get your message across the right way? How can you start raking in those requests to be hired by the right people you can help best?</description></item><item><title>Branding through events (Networking Part 4)</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/branding-through-events-networking-part-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 21:58:58 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/branding-through-events-networking-part-4/</guid><description>The types of events you attend shape your personal branding.
Events overload I know you’re part of at least one group that has something to do with networking. And you also get asked a lot to attend major or minor events. It sometimes feels overwhelming and you can’t decide which events to attend. I’ll give you this tool to make a quick yet informed decision of which of all the events will really be the productive one for you.</description></item><item><title>Bring value first (Networking Part 3)</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/bring-value-first-networking-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 06:00:21 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/bring-value-first-networking-part-3/</guid><description>Bring value to your network first the rest will come later. Have you built your valuable and strong network already? If so, you know that seeking to bring value to your network first will make the key difference. People experienced in networking will mostly concur. I’ll list different ways of contributing value to your network in just a second.
Contribute according to your abilities People generally want to improve upon their current status.</description></item><item><title>Say goodbye to everyone (Networking Part 2)</title><link>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/say-goodbye-to-everyone-networking-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 06:00:16 +0000</pubDate><author>cheret.en</author><guid>https://new.cheret.de/2016/10/say-goodbye-to-everyone-networking-part-2/</guid><description>Now here’s one networking advice I can give you. I’ve had countless opportunities through this seemingly small but impactful gesture. On the surface it’s quite simple: Always say goodbye to everyone when you’re leaving an event! And I know that it’s more complicated than that. Give me a moment to explain, though. It will become essential in your networking toolkit.
Everyone&amp;rsquo;s so busy So you’ve been at this busy event and you only knew half of the people there.</description></item></channel></rss>